Now, let's start HIKIME是 ○メンタージョスTV~~~
We've been talking about the last show.
How was it?
How was it, Juri?
We've been thinking about the members.
We want to be the king of all.
All of us?
That's it.
Three of us are done.
Who's the king of all?
Four of us?
Three of us.
Today is the fourth.
Who was the king of all?
The last time was the punishment game.
These two.
We'll reflect on it.
That's right.
If you think about it,
I think it's someone's king.
Someone's king.
We've been thinking about the king of
all.
We've been making it.
I think it's good to have everyone.
If everyone is gone, it's like a fool.
But it was really good.
I thought of a really good idea.
I don't know.
What is it?
It's like a charity.
Anyone can buy it.
I thought of that.
That's good.
It's a good idea.
I'll make a good suggestion.
It's like a good suggestion meeting.
It's like a charity.
I'll make it.
We'll have a good suggestion meeting.
What are we doing this week?
As you know,
I'd like to decide on KITTY.
I've been waiting for this.
I'm confident.
Are you confident?
Yes.
Then,
I have no reason.
Who else is confident?
Yes.
Why are you two so excited?
Isn't it strange?
Because we're next to each other.
That's right.
Haru and Julia are always next to me.
But this time,
everyone is equal.
It's not about the past.
Everyone is equal.
So, Aki and Julia...
Julia?
Julia is also...
It's fun.
It's a round table.
It's far.
It's okay.
We're the same age.
That's right.
We're not the same age.
We're not.
We're not close.
It's so far, but I'm always next to
you.
It's amazing.
I'm sorry.
It's a round table.
Aki, please read the usual question.
We're going to give you a quiz about
Hitochan.
Hitochan answers the questions by
writing a line.
You have to guess what she wrote.
It's easy if you know about Hitochan.
Let's do our best.
Please watch the next video and follow
us on Twitter.
Let's get started.
There is a game.
If you get one question right, you can
get 1 REO-kun point.
If you can't get the most, you can get
a penalty.
I'm scared.
Last time, we played a game called
Namakemono.
The last time was Kumano.
Are you ready?
Let's get started.
This program is brought to you by the
six members who work hard to promote
something exciting.
Subscribe to our channel here!
Be honest & tell me your stories
The first!
I think you know what this is.
Bye bye!
What is the color of the toothbrush
that Chito-chan and Chitose-chan use?
I used it!
That's it!
This is the easiest one.
I forgot to say it, but the time limit
is 1 minute.
40 seconds left.
I didn't even choose 1 minute.
You didn't choose it.
I didn't choose it.
Oh, you didn't choose it.
Then, it's okay.
It's okay.
I think it's right.
Is Hiyorin okay?
I don't know.
Kaito.
I'm sure your answers are the same.
Do you agree, Mahiru?
Yes.
What is your favorite color?
Let's see.
One, two, three.
Ta-da!
Pink!
Red!
I love it!
I love it.
I don't have to ask you why.
I wrote it down again.
Red.
Do you want to go to the moon?
1st or 2nd floor.
We can go to the moon.
Let's watch our world tour!
And Pudding.
What's the color of your toothbrush
that you've been using?
The color of my toothbrush that I've
been using since I was in elementary
school is...
Pink!
So, the answer is Kanamin, Junia and
Aki-chan!
It's like Leo-kun!
Leo-kun points!
What's the color of your toothbrush
that you've been using since you were in
elementary school?
It's long!
So, Aki-chan, Kanamin and Junia got one
point each!
Let's move on to the next question!
The next question is...
This one is easy too!
What's the color of your toothbrush
that you've been using since you were in
elementary school?
The color of your toothbrush is
perfect!
But this is...
Wait, this is...
Everything is perfect!
This is also a perfect spelling.
You can tell that it's perfect even if
you see it in the answer sheet.
But it's okay if you see it in the
answer sheet.
That's true.
But you can't see it in the answer
sheet.
I think it's okay.
Wait, I'm so confused.
I think I've said it before.
I think so too.
I think it's a mistake.
I think I've said it a few times.
What's the name of the book you read
yesterday?
Hitokan Shishinjyuu.
I think I've read it before.
What's the time?
20 seconds left.
It was too long!
It's either one of them.
10 seconds left.
Which one?
I can't help it.
I can't tell which one is the name.
Please think about it with me.
I'm done.
Please write your answer together.
Ready, go!
First love.
Wait, let me see.
It's the same word at the beginning.
Yes, I think so too.
Only F and L are the same.
Everyone, please show us the same word.
I think F and L are the same.
F and...
Isn't it first?
First.
Please check the next video!
What?
What is the title of your photo book?
My title is...
Konnomiya!
I think you know the title of the first
song.
But I'm not sure if you can spell it.
Especially Piyo-chan.
You're making it shorter.
I think you're writing it wrong.
The answer is...
FI...
FILS?
You saw it yesterday, right?
Yes, I did.
So,
Kanamin, Julia and Oharu
got it right!
We got it right!
Aki-chan's was all in 5 letters.
I got it right.
But,
it's okay.
It was close.
But, I got it right.
Thank you.
Unfortunately,
we can't give you points.
Kiyochan, you got it right.
I did.
I got it right.
I was so confident.
I got 0 points for one person.
Really?
Is it the same as the first letter of
Breakfast?
No.
It's not.
Breakfast is F, A.
It's different from that.
Let's get back to it.
We still have some questions.
Let's move on to the next question.
The next question is...
I can tell if I look at it.
Let's go.
Ta-da.
What is Hitochan's present?
I don't know.
Who is the most popular character in
the current era?
Inumaki, Kaneki, and who is the other
one?
Seriously?
I think it's going to change soon.
These two are popular.
I don't know.
I'll give you a hint.
Some people don't know anime.
Some people don't like anime.
But, they watch anime.
Wait.
I don't know.
Some people don't like otaku.
Some people don't like anime.
Wait.
Can I say the general answer?
The general answer is correct.
What is it?
I don't know.
You know the character, don't you?
I know.
What?
I know the character.
You know the character?
What?
I'm sure it's correct.
I know it since I was a child.
Right?
I'm sure you know it.
10, 9, 8, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Did you all get it?
Please answer it together.
Ready, go.
Shin-chan.
Conan-kun.
The person who was in Ghibli.
That's right.
Then, who is it?
It's close.
VTR.
What?
The person who was in Ghibli.
Who is the person who is in the
picture?
The person who I like the most is Haul.
I like Haul the most.
I saw it on TV.
I thought Haul is cool and I like him.
I like these three people including
Haul.
It's too funny.
I like all of them.
I like Shin-chan.
I like Conan-kun too.
I'm looking forward to the movie that
will be released on April 16th and 17th.
I'm late.
Aki-chan.
It's funny.
I like Aki-chan.
I watch it every day.
Every day?
She's cute.
She's like a monkey.
I got it.
Shiori-chan is correct.
I was told that it's an anime.
I see.
I was wondering if I could put this in
the anime.
I thought it's a Jujutsu Kaisen.
Because she is small.
She is small.
It was cool.
I did Haul.
I'll give you points for Shiori's
anime.
Thank you for watching!
I know this one.
Ta-da!
What is Hito-chan's favorite word on
the official website of the Super-
Touhou?
I know this one.
I often say this.
When I'm asked if there is a word I
like, I always answer.
But it's a good word.
If you don't know, you can write a good
word.
I know this one.
You haven't changed.
I haven't changed.
I know this one.
This is a word I often say.
Please answer together.
One, two, three.
People shine because they have dreams.
No.
I know this one.
People shine because they have dreams.
They work hard to move forward.
I know this one.
I changed it.
I want to tell you the answer.
I'll change it.
It's cool.
What is the answer?
Please show us the video.
What is your favorite word on the
official website of Super-Touhou?
I've talked about this word in various
places.
The answer is...
People shine because they have dreams.
I'll change it.
People shine.
I thought it was easy.
Hiyoyon, you're not a good speaker.
I thought of the word sun.
But, the sun was in the way.
I couldn't think of other words.
But, I understood the word when I saw
the mirror.
I understood it as a part of my life.
I'll change it.
People shine because they have dreams.
This is a good word.
It's a perfect word for Aki-chan.
I like it.
Maybe, it'll be on the official
website.
I'll say what I like.
I think it'll be a lot today.
I think it's a good word.
It's written by Kite-chan.
I'll keep this word in my heart as I
become an idol.
But, it's a bit...
It's a bit short.
I'm not in a good mood.
I didn't press it.
Karami-san, you're a good speaker.
I'm looking forward to it.
I can't remember the words.
It's fun.
We have half of the time left.
Please look forward to the next video!
This is a bit difficult.
My mom said that I might have written
this on a blog.
But this is difficult.
This is the one.
I'll go.
I was learning swimming when I was in
elementary school.
My teacher said that I should quit if I
passed the crawl test.
My dad said that I did my best until I
got to the crawl test.
What does that mean?
I don't know.
I thought you were a swimmer.
I did it until I was in the lower grade
of elementary school.
I did it until I got the crawl test.
I can't do butterfly, but I didn't like
it.
I wanted to quit, but I was in the
lower grade of elementary school.
I was 10 or 19 years old.
I did my best because of my dad's
words.
I'm a girl.
Is your dad impressed?
My dad didn't say that.
I didn't?
But my dad said that I was persuasive.
Please think about it.
I think you are a cute girl.
Did you write down your answer?
Yes.
Please write down your answer.
I'll be popular if I can swim.
I'll marry a swimmer.
I can't marry her.
I wanted to marry my dad.
Swimmers are cool.
I can be a princess.
I can be Ariel.
I'm the same.
But my dad is...
He is persuasive.
I'm a cool girl.
I don't know.
My dad is Ariel.
I'll write down my answer.
I'm the closest to my dad.
Please write down your answer.
Hitochan, who was learning swimming in
elementary school, wanted to quit
swimming.
But she did her best because of her
dad's words.
What is that?
I was learning swimming, but I wasn't
good at it.
I told my dad that I wanted to quit
swimming.
But my dad said that I should be a
swimmer when I was an adult.
Because I was a good swimmer.
I wanted to be a swimmer.
I was 10 years old when I was told
that.
I wanted to date, so I learned
swimming.
That's cute.
I told my dad that I should be a
swimmer when I date.
I told him that there was no one who
swam in the black water.
I was a swimmer.
You were a swimmer.
I told my dad that I couldn't swim
because of my face.
But he said that there was no one who
swam in the black water.
So, I swam in the black water.
That's a dream.
Maybe my mom saw me when I was dating
with my dad.
She fell in love with me.
I didn't expect that.
I was a swimmer.
You have a different style.
I have a different style.
You were a swimmer.
Do you swim?
I'm a dog.
You are a dog.
I don't know if there is a dog.
I'm a swimmer.
Women should practice swimming.
The correct answer is...
0.
It was fun.
Next, let's move on to the next
question.
This is easy.
Kanami might know the answer.
I don't know.
I'm sure you all know the answer.
What is Hito's favorite item?
There were only two items.
I think the first one is the best.
I think I know the answer.
I have three.
Please tell me the name of the item.
You can know the answer if you watch
the fan club.
You watch it, right?
I saw you eating natto.
I did.
Then...
Oh, it's over.
Did you eat it?
Yes, I did.
I smelled it and waited for 30 seconds.
I've seen you eat it.
It has nothing to do with natto.
Can I?
Yes.
That's it.
Well, then, please answer.
One, two, three.
Doraemon.
Dekinmon.
Tomato.
Resta Aemon.
Apple.
Dekinmon.
Well, then, please show the correct
answer.
What is your favorite food?
My favorite food is sweet potato.
I think I like sweet potato the most
among all the foods in the world.
By the way, you can also grill sweet
potatoes.
So, it's sweet potato.
First of all,
Yakiimo.
Yakiimo is correct.
Is it steamed sweet potato?
I like steamed sweet potato.
I like Oizu.
Oizu?
I thought Oizu was a Japanese sweet
potato.
Oikoshi.
Steamed sweet potato.
It's not a potato, but sweet potato.
It's not a potato.
It's sweet potato.
Sweet potato.
So,
Aki and Tanami are correct.
I can't eat potatoes.
I have an allergic reaction.
I can't eat it.
But I love sweet potatoes.
I talked to Aki about her favorite
food.
And I asked Tanami to eat it.
She answered me.
Tomato is...
It's bear.
I like bear.
It's apple.
I like apple.
I know you like many kinds of apple.
I like apple, too.
But I like sweet potato the most.
Kanae is correct.
I was watching it.
3 points.
Julia is correct.
Aki is correct.
Thank you for watching! Please
subscribe to us!
We are the same age, aren't we?
We are the same age.
We are very close.
Let's keep in touch!
Let's move on to the next question.
Here is the next question.
What is Kuro's favorite food?
I don't know.
Please tell us.
I've been craving it lately.
Lately?
I don't know.
For my family?
Because I like my sister.
It's not for family.
I feel like I'm wrong.
Let's go.
Please give us the answer.
Ready, go.
Oatmeal gratin.
Meat bun.
Please show us the video.
What is your specialty?
Hito-chan's... No, my specialty is...
Pumpkin soup and hamburger!
I'm told to make these two dishes.
I think I'll like them if I make them.
That's my specialty.
Why are you all drinking?
I'm sorry.
I've heard of it.
I've told you!
I've told you.
I like the hamburger of McDonald's.
Which one?
I like McDonald's hamburger.
I make it with that.
I like the pumpkin soup every autumn.
So, it was pumpkin soup and hamburger!
The answer is...
It was melon!
Bye!
Hito-chan is shocked!
Everyone knows about Hito-chan!
Hito-chan will cry!
Hito-chan is shocked!
Please come back next time!
Let's go!
Here we go!
What's the juice that you liked as a
kid and as a high schooler?
Juice?
Something delicious!
Something healthy?
You said it!
Juice?
When I was a kid, I didn't like sweet
stuff.
I didn't like whipped cream.
I didn't like sweet stuff.
But I started to like sweet stuff when
I was a high schooler.
I'm a high schooler.
It's sweet.
It's light.
Is it not here?
I started to look at it since I was in
high school.
And then I started to drink it.
I said too much.
I was like, this?
I usually say it.
Let's see the first question.
Cocoa? Milk tea?
Frappuccino?
Mascarpone?
Milk tea?
Let's do it again.
Cocoa?
Milk tea?
Frappuccino?
Mascarpone?
Milk tea?
Let's do it again.
I agree.
I don't drink it when I was little.
You're right.
I agree with you.
I don't drink it.
Please give me a comment.
I didn't like it when I was a kid, but
what's your favorite juice since high
school?
Cream soda!
I was a little bit tired when I was a
kid.
I didn't like it when I was a kid, but
it became popular when I was a high
school student.
I thought it was good and tried it.
I liked it since high school.
I've never seen you drink it.
I drank it at a cafe.
I drank it at a lesson.
It's a little bit weird.
I drank Royal Milk Tea the other day.
Who is it?
If you say it's me, it's Royal Milk
Tea.
Next question.
This one is easy.
Here we go.
What is Hitochan's favorite food?
She eats a lot and she's particular
about it.
I'm not sure.
What? Bread?
Bread?
I wonder if it's the same as the normal
one.
I wonder.
I'm sure everyone eats it often.
Everyone?
Everyone eats it often.
It's a variety.
I'll eat it.
Did you eat it?
Yes.
Then, please answer together.
One, two, three.
What is it?
Melon bread with chocolate Pokemon
sticker.
Bread.
Croissant.
Steamed bread.
Tamon bread.
Oh, that's right.
But I can't eat it.
I can't eat it.
What is your favorite bread?
I love bread. I eat a lot of bread.
I like bread the most.
My mom always buys me delicious bread.
I'm happy to eat delicious bread.
So the answer was bread.
I ate it this morning.
Julia is correct.
I like egg bread.
I like steamed bread.
I often buy steamed bread at the
station.
I eat it.
I also like croissant.
Croissant is delicious.
I eat it often.
Julia is correct.
I'm happy.
Julia and Kanae got 3 points.
Oharu and Aki got 2 points.
Hiyorin got 1 point.
Yorin got 2 points.
How many points did I get?
2 points.
I got 2 points.
Thank you for watching.
I'm sure I used it.
I'm sorry, but I didn't know the final
question until today.
I'll show you.
I'm going to show you the final
question.
How long does it take for Fuku-chan to
get up and leave the house?
Please answer.
What do you mean by time?
I measured the time it took to get up
and leave the house.
Why do you measure it like a math?
I measured the time it took to get up
and leave the house.
I opened the front door.
I can't answer anything.
Did you have lunch?
I just had a meal.
It's been a week.
I'm tired.
It's time.
Did you write it?
Please write your answers.
3 hours and 30 minutes.
2 hours and 40 minutes.
2 hours and 45 minutes.
You wrote it.
I'm tired.
By the way,
did you get up before you went out?
I think so.
I think I got up around 2 hours ago.
Did you get up?
Yes.
I slept a lot.
I'm tired.
3 hours?
How about you, Aki?
8 hours.
I woke up at 4am.
You are young.
No, I'm not.
What are you doing?
My grandma is sleeping.
I'm sleeping too.
That's your grandma.
You are a troublemaker.
I'm fine.
Well, everyone.
As a fighter dancer,
I'll do my best.
What time did you get up and leave the
house?
What time did I get up and leave the
I got up at 4 o'clock.
I think you all have the same image as
me.
You often say that you got up at 10
minutes and got ready.
I think you have the same image.
I didn't get up early today.
I got up early in the morning, but I
got up at 4 o'clock.
I'm alone.
So, I was the first to get up early.
I did it.
You are weak.
I got up at 8 o'clock and got up at 12
o'clock.
So, I got up at 4 o'clock.
I usually get up at 30 minutes early.
I got up a little late today.
So, I got up at 4 o'clock.
So, we are the first to get up early.
We are the second to get up early.
That's all for the questions.
The result is...
Kanami 3 points, Julia 3 points, Ohami
4 points, Aki 2 points, Hiyorin...
So, the last place of the Hitokao
competition is...
We have been together for 6 years and
graduated from the same high school.
Someone is going to collapse.
We have been together for 6 years and
graduated from the same high school.
Hiyori, who came to see my photo album
yesterday, is the last place.
The winner is...
How do you feel now?
I've been with you for a long time.
I know.
You're a good girl.
You know me well.
I feel like I'm winning.
But you and Julia are...
Yes.
If it wasn't for the points, we would
have been tied.
We were tied.
We were.
But we're tied.
You got 2 points for the action.
You still have a year to go, but you
still got 2 points.
I don't know.
You got it wrong.
If you got the first love right, you
and Aki-chan would be the same.
That's a problem of the brain.
I like the dojo, but I'm not good at
it.
I'm actually bored.
If Hiyorin is the last, you'll have to
play a penalty game.
You'll have to imitate my favorite
character, Haul.
Haul is very cool, so I hope you'll
imitate me.
Please use the lines you come up with.
It's a dance of moving the pole.
Sofiii!
Sofii, where are you?
Sofii!
Sofii, come on!
You!
No, we were definitely dating in the
past.
But you were bewitched by a strange
witch and became like that.
I love you!
Me too.
Yeah.
So, Sofii, even if you become like
that,
I'll be waiting for you.
Howl, Howl loves you.
So, why don't you live in my castle,
Howl's moving castle?
Howl's castle.
Thank you.
See you next week.
Bye-bye.
Stop it!
No?
That's a kiss scene.
Please subscribe to our channel.
So, what is it?
Sofie will kiss Haru.
So, Haru, what?
Haru, what?
What?
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
Bye-bye!
I hope we can continue to create
wonderful scenery together!
That day it should actually, happen
I think I will have the right to get my
dream
The real me
It should finally, happen
Right now is the perfect hour
To reach out for your hand
So don't get lost
You can push through
I want to erase the truth
The more I run, the more I get
Today is brighter than anything
I want to erase the feelings
Pyon! Pyon!
Let's start!
Hello!
If you got the best score,
If you think Hiori's haul was cool,
Please subscribe and click the good
button!
I'm waiting for your comments!
I want to share my feelings with you
There's still a view I've never seen
before
Let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye
Thank you for yesterday
The city after the rain is colorful
Draw a piece of the future on the
canvas of my damaged heart
It will guide me
Now is the night, and the reason for my
tears
When I'm lost, I remember right away
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the sound
of the rain drops
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a flower, the sound of
the rain drops
I wear a rainbow dress
La la la la la la
Thank you for watching!